翻译:满庭芳香    校对:魏剑锋 交流QQ：931061361
本字幕仅供交流学习  严禁用于任何商业用途
www.xoases.com
大玩家
阿姆斯特丹
欢迎来到里芒特
Welcome to Le Monte.
我是这间展览室的主人
I am the owner of this showroom.
这是我的经理乔普拉先生
This is my manager Mr. Chopra.
塔帕夫人
Mrs. Thappar.
欢迎
Welcome.
你丈夫打过电话了
Your husband called.
稍后还汇给了我一张空白支票
He also sent a blank check,in advance.
显摆
Show off.
喂  - 嘿  宝贝
Yes.- Hey, baby.
购物怎么样
How is your shopping going?
你就不能找家别的展览室
Couldn't you find another showroom..
汇空头支票?
..to send your blank check.
为什么  怎么了
Why? What happened?
这啥也没有
There's nothing here.
放松点  把电话给乔普拉
Just relax. Give the phone to Chopra.
我丈夫
My husband.
你好  先生
Hello, sir.
听着  明天是我们结婚一周年纪念日
Listen, tomorrow is our first anniversary.
我要送给我妻子最贵的项链作为礼物
And I want to gift the most expensive necklace to my wife.
难道你没想过
Don't you think..
第一年你就这么大手笔...
..you're paying a big price for your first year.
别胡扯
Stop blabbering.
现在我觉得第一年的纪念日我就要离婚了
Now I feel I will get divorced on my first anniversary.
不是  不是  先生
No, no, no, sir.
只要我们在这
How can you get such a big happiness..
你会感到相当幸福的
..as long as we are there.
闭嘴
Just shut up.
他说什么
What is he saying?
他说你的展览室太差劲了
He is saying your showroom is pathetic.
去把"撒马尔罕玫瑰"拿来
Go and get the 'Rose Of Samarkand'.
恭喜你  先生
Congratulations, sir.
我们有"撒马尔罕玫瑰"
We are getting the 'Rose Of Samarkand'.
给你  夫人
Yes, ma'am.
嗯  - 现在高兴了吧
Yes. - Are you happy now?
为你呈现"撒马尔罕玫瑰"
Presenting to you the 'Rose Of Samarkand'.
由伊朗艺术家精制而成
Exquisite finish by Iranian artist.
告诉我
Just tell me this.
如果我买这个
If I buy this how drastically..
对我丈夫的空白支票会有多大影响
..will it affect my husband's bank balance?
就像游泳池里的四桶水
Like four buckets of water from the swimming pool.
就这样?
That's all.
我是说他只剩
I mean four buckets of water..
四桶水了  其它都没了
..is all that he will be left with,the rest will be gone.
那我就要这个了
Then I will take this.
早上好  -早上好
Good morning. - Morning, morning.
你好  举起手来
Hello, and hands up.
你也是
You, hands up.
听着  你拿不走这个
Look, you can't get away with this.
这栋大厦警卫森严
This building is heavily guarded.
我的保安...
And my guards..
你按那个  我就按这个
You press that.. I will press this.
你不知道我丈夫是谁...
You don't know who my husband is.
抓住他
Go catch him.
快点
Hurry up.
惊喜
Surprising.
一个贼破坏了我的购物  你看起来很生气
A thief spoiled my shopping and you are looking angry.
你为什么按警报器
Why did you sound the alarm?
我想看你表演  查理马斯卡伦哈斯
I wanted to see you in action, Charlie Mascarenhas.
现在高兴了吧
'Are you happy now?'
购物完了来接我
'Pick me up once you finish your shopping.
大家早上好
Good morning.
你好  举起手来
Hello, and hands up.
你好
Hello.
大家早上好
Good morning.
你就是我的灵感
You are my inspiration.
把灵感留给你自己吧
Keep your inspiration to yourself..
把我的那份给我
..and give me my share.
你已经拿着了
You already took that.
你不知道我丈夫是谁
You don't know who my husband is
你是个真正的艺术家  查理
You are a real artist, Charlie.
走吧  咱们去庆祝
Come on, let's go celebrate.
你知道规矩的
You know the rules.
工作之前和之后的六个月...
Six months before and after the job..- We won't see each other.
我们都不见面
现在才六个月
Its only six months.
俄罗斯  六个月后
德波拉斯基
Debrovsky.
你好  请在滴声后留言
Hi. Please leave your message after the beep.
你好  希拉
Hello, Shaila.
一个月前我寄给你个包裹
I sent you a parcel a month ago..
并和你说过如果我有任何不测
..and said that if anything happens to me..
把包裹寄给查理
..then send that parcel to Charlie.
看来现在是时候了
Seems like its time to send that parcel to Charlie.
Where is the plan?
在哪  快告诉我
Where is it? Tell me.
果阿
希拉  请节哀顺便
Shaila, my heart felt condolences.
你丈夫去世还不到四天
It's been less than four days since your husband died..
你就不守丧了
..and you already stopped mourning.
怎么了  你没看到我穿黑色衣服吗
Why? Don't you see my black dress?
干嘛叫我来这
Anyway? Why did you call me here?
瑞吉死前一个月从莫斯科寄来了这个
Raj sent this from Moscow a month before he died, for you.
他说他要是有什么不测
He said that if anything happens to him..
我就把这个交给你
..then I should give it too you.
你童年的记忆那一套玩意
Your childhood memory and all that crap.
谢谢
Thank you.
查理
Charlie.
瑞吉留下些东西给你
Raj has left something for you.
如果你想要就是你的
It can be yours if you want.
你很性感  希拉  - 我知道
You are hot, Shaila. - I know.
但还不足以让我背叛我的朋友
But not so much that I betray my friend.
我了解瑞吉  他留给我的远不止这么多
And if I know Raj, he has left much more for me.
再见
See you.
整个图书馆都要是他的了
The entire library is waiting to be his.
他却只关心这本书
And he's interested in that book.
如果你看到这张光碟
If you're watching this DVD..
爆炸新闻是...
..then the breaking news is..
别这样  又来了
Come on, not again.
悉尼
你好  南娜  你又黑进了我的电脑
Hello, Naina. You hacked into my computer again.
我能怎么办呢  查理
What can I do, Charlie?
只有这样你才能打电话给我
That's the only way to make you call me.
南娜  不开玩笑
Naina, be serious.
我有个很重要的光碟要看
I have to watch an important DVD.
希望你没在看黄片
I hope you are not watching porn.
我还不知道一个受过高等教育的
I didn't know that a well educated..
注册会计师还会看黄片
..chartered accountant type of person also watches porn.
我不是在看黄片
I am not watching porn.
管它的
Whatever.
我只是想告诉你我完成学业了
I just wanted to tell you that I have finished my course.
托您洪福  现在我是金牌
For your information, now I am a Masters in Computers..
电脑专家
..with a gold medal.
不错啊
Well done.
嘿  哇哦
Hey, wow.
嘿  你好吗
Hey. How are you doing?
来我车上  我们去兜风
Come jump in my car we'll go for a drive.
喂  南娜
Hang out, do some stuff.
来啊
Come on.
南娜  - 第二个好消息是
Naina. - The second good news is..
明天我就回印度了
..that I am coming back to India tomorrow.
真的?太好了!
Really? Fantastic.
现在帮我修修电脑
Good, now fix my computer.
在你的电脑上温柔地输入我的名字
Just type my name on your computer sweetly..
就好了
..and it will be fixed.
但要温柔地
But sweetly, okay.
好  温柔地
Fine. Sweetly.
如果你看到这张光碟
If you're watching this DVD..
爆炸新闻是
..then the breaking news is that..
俄罗斯的黑手党杀了我
..the Russian Mafia has killed me.
今天我要给你讲最后一个故事
Today I am going to tell you a last story.
故事发生在1915年
This story started in 1915.
一战期间德军
During World War 1 when the German army..
攻占了罗马尼亚首都布加勒斯特
..reached Romania's capital Bucharest then..
罗马尼亚政府为了保命而逃跑
..the Romanian government decided to flee for their lives.
他们带走了重要文件和珍宝
They took important documents and their treasures along.
俄国沙皇为表示他们是友好邻邦
The Czar of Russia agreed to keep their treasure..
同意代他们保管这些财物
..showing that they are good neighbors.
直到战争结束
Until the war ended.
所以  在1916年10月15日
So in this way, on 15 October 1916..
成吨的黄金用火车运往俄国
..tons of gold were sent to Russia by train.
但是战争结束后
But by the end of the war..
俄国政府变卦了
..the Russian government changed.
新政府不待见罗马尼亚
The new government refused to entertain Romania.
"你们在说什么黄金?"
''Which gold are you talking about?''
过去的95年  那批黄金
And for the past 95 years that gold..
被锁在沙皇的冬宫里
..has been locked up in the Russian Czar's winter palace.
但是这个故事今年发生了转变
But the twist in the story came in this year..
俄罗斯承认了历史错误
..when Russia finally accepted that what happened was wrong.
今天10月15日
And on this 15th October..
那批黄金将会被运到罗马尼亚
..that gold will be shipped back to Romania.
怎么来就怎么回去
Exactly the same way, by train.
用火车运输
Just like it was brought here.
纯罗马尼亚黄金
Pure Romanian gold..
在今天市值十亿元
..which is worth 1 billion in today's date.
如果罗马尼亚95年来
If Romania could survive for 95 years without the gold..
没有那批金子也活得好好的
那么未来也会活得不错
..then it can do so in future as well.
它也不再属于俄罗斯了
And it never belonged to Russia anyway.
当某些东西无人认领时
When something's unclaimed..
它是属于上帝呢还是我们这样的正人君子?
..then it either belongs to God or to decent people like us.
不是吗
Isn't it?
在我走前  我想给你最后一条建议
Before I leave I want to give you a final tip.
别再犯我这样的错误
Don't make the mistake that I did.
这不是一个人的工作
This is not a job for one person.
你需要一个团队  查理
You need a team, Charlie.
世界顶尖玩家组成的团队
A team of the world's best players.
只有一个人能帮你组建团队
And there's just one man who can get you that team.
我们的老师  维克托
Our guru, Victor.
维克托先生
Victor sir.
这里很安全
This is the safe of the house..
哪里有劫案
..where the robbery was committed.
三个星期都有
Its been three weeks..
但是我们还没逮到贼
..but we couldn't apprehend the thief yet.
如果要抓住一个狡猾的贼
If you want to catch a cunning thief..
要试图了解他
..then try to understand him.
要用贼的思维而不是警察的  - 记下来
Not like a policeman but think like a thief. - Note it down.
贼有三条规则
Thieves have three rules..
使他们不同于警察
..that differentiate them from policemen.
第一条
Rule no.1.
每个贼都是个艺术家
Every thief is a kind of an artist.
没有贼会背叛他的艺术
And no thief betrays his art.
警察可能会忘了他的职责  但贼不会
A policeman might forget his duty but not a thief.
第二条
Rule no.2.
只有警察才会退休  贼不会
Only policemen retire. Not thieves.
一日为贼  终生为贼
Once a thief always a thief.
第三条  也是最重要的一条
Rule no.3 and the most important rule.
当警察绞尽脑汁时
When a policeman is tired of racking his brains..
贼才刚刚开始思考
..that's where a thief starts using his.
我怎么觉得他在污蔑我们
Why do I feel that he is slandering us?
维克托先生  你想表达什么
Victor sir. What do you want to say?
我想说你找错对象了
I want to say that you have lodged the wrong FIR.
这不是价值40万的珠宝盗窃案
This isn't a case of robbery of jewelry worth 40 lakhs.
进来  帮帮我
Come on, just help me here.
我们仔细看这两张照片
Come, let's watch those two pictures carefully.
一张是盗窃前  一张是盗窃后
One before the robbery and the other after it.
看出两张照片的不同了吗
Do you see the difference in both the pictures?
我不知道
I don't understand.
我是说贼想偷走马里卡先生的画
I mean the thief wanted Mr.Malik's painting and he took it.
用赝品来代替  - 赝品?
And he put up a fake painting instead. - Fake painting?
看这
Take a look.
看  这是真品
Look, this is the real painting.
看这里的签名
Look at the signature stroke here.
比较短  是不是
Its small, isn't it?
这幅就是赝品
And this one is fake.
看这幅下面的签名
Look at the signature stroke below this one.
比较长
It's longer.
It's longer, isn't it?
这是个女人所为
This is the work of a woman.
你怎么知道
How can you say that?
我的会计师会告诉你
My CA will tell you that.
案发前花瓶在这
Before the robbery this vase was here.
案发后它自动地移动这了
But after the robbery it automatically shifted here.
男人才不会干这么有审美观的事情
These aesthetics can never be of a man.
你们现在明白了?
Do you understand now?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
抓到了贼要给我寄糖来哦
Do send me sweets when you catch the thief.
当然  先生
Of course, sir.
怎么样  - 挺好
How are you? - Fine.
我女儿南娜...  - 她已经长大了
And my child Naina.. - She has now grown up.
噢  是啊  已经十年了
Oh, yes. It's been 10 years. 10 years.
她还不想见我吗
Doesn't she want to meet me?
她昨天才回来的  还没调整过来时差
She just returned yesterday. She is suffering from jetlag.
随她吧  我了解她
Let it be. I know her.
她就像我一样
She is like me.
她不会那么轻易被说服的
She won't be convinced so easily.
还有件事
Grandpa, there was another thing.
这是你在希姆拉镇买的80英亩土地
This is the 80 acre land which you bought near Shimla.
这是学生宿舍
This is our student dormitory.
这是员工宿舍
These are the staff quarters.
它们完美无暇
And they will be so good that..
印度最好的老师都想在这教书
..the best teachers of India would want to teach here.
这里为孤儿们提供所有设施
And all the facilities will be available here..
帮助立足于世
..for orphan children to help them compete in the world.
总之
In short.
这是我未完成的梦想
My incomplete dream.
你的梦想会实现
Your dream can be fulfilled.
怎么
How?
我是你的会计师
I am your CA.
我得为你考虑些事
I must have thought of something.
你想的都是歪门邪道
You surely didn't think of anything straight.
如果你要在这个拥有十亿人口的国家
If you want to fulfill your dreams..
实现你的梦想
..in this country with a population of 100 crore..
肯定是歪门邪道
..then you can't think straight.
是你教我的
You taught me this.
你一定听说了瑞吉的死
You must have heard about Raj's death.
他不该一个人行动
He shouldn't have attempted this job alone.
这就是瑞吉证明给我们的结果
This is the lead that Raj has provided us.
这有份我深思熟虑的计划
And this has the plan that I have thought about.
但是我需要你的帮助
But I need your help.
还有一些玩家
And some players as well.
只有你才能帮我
Which only you can provide me.
你知道我已经退休了
You know I have retired.
第二条
Rule no.2.
只有警察才会退休
Only policemen retire.
你已经实现了我的  瑞吉的还有很多人的梦想
You have fulfilled mine, Raj and dreams of so many others.
我只是想你能实现梦想
I just want your only dream to be fulfilled.
叔叔
Grandpa.
南娜让我提醒你别忘了承诺
Naina was asking me to remind you about some promise.
把这个给南娜
Give this to Naina.
告诉她  这些是她爸爸在监狱
And tell her that her papa has earned this..
编织篮子挣来的
..by weaving baskets in jail.
爸爸怎么样
How is papa?
他还好吗
Is he fine?
你提醒他我的承诺没
Did you remind him about my promise?
给你  你爸爸让我把这个给你
Here, madam. Your father has sent this for you.
他辛勤工作挣来的
His hard earned money.
你哭了  - 没  我才没有
You are crying. - No, I am not.
是的  你哭了
Yes, you are crying.
我爱他  查理
I love him, Charlie.
我很想他  - 没事了
I miss him. - Its okay.
三个星期
Three weeks.
之后就只有爸爸和我
After that it will be just my father and me.
即使他的会计师要见他
Even his CA will have to fix an appointment through me..
也要经过我的批准  好吗
..to meet him, okay.
没问题
Done.
三个?
Three?
这在印度是合法的?
Has this become legal in India as well?
南娜  我都不认识她们
Come on, Naina, I don't even know these girls.
现在我明白了
Now I get it.
她们是你的财务顾问
So this is your financial consultancy.
嘿  查理
Hey, Charlie.
生日快乐  查理
Happy birthday, Charlie.
∮ 嘿  查理 ∮
''Hey, Charlie.''
∮ 为什么就这么走了 ∮
''Why you got to be like that?''
∮ 今夜属于你  让我给你惊喜 ∮
''Tonight is your night, let me delight you.''
∮ 查理天使 ∮
''Charlie's Angels.''
∮ 坐立不安 ∮
''This restlessness.''
∮ 甜蜜痛苦 ∮
''The sweet pain.''
∮ 无眠之夜 ∮
''The sleepless nights.''
∮ 查理天使 ∮
''Charlie's Angels.''
∮ 坐立不安 ∮
''This restlessness.''
∮ 甜蜜痛苦 ∮
''The sweet pain.''
∮ 不眠之夜 ∮
''The sleepless nights.''
∮ 这是爱的效果 ∮
''It's the effect of love.''
∮ 旅途艰辛 ∮
''It's a difficult journey.''
∮ 我需要你的支持 ∮
''I need your support.''
∮ 让我步履轻盈 ∮
''Make my journey easier.''
∮ 她已疯狂  上帝  让她清醒 ∮
''She crazy, Lord,
give her some sense.''
∮ 她已疯狂  上帝  让她清醒 ∮
''She crazy, Lord,
give her some sense.''
∮ 她的光芒微弱 ∮
''Her stars are weak.''
∮ 她看起来不妙 ∮
''Her intentions don't look good.''
∮ 她生命面临危险 ∮
''Her life's in danger.''
∮ 上帝啊  让她清醒 ∮
''Lord, give her some sense.''
∮ 她已疯狂  上帝  让她清醒 ∮
''She crazy, Lord, give her some sense.''
∮ 人人都会知晓你的爱情故事 ∮
''Everyone will know of your love story.''
∮ 即使你不讲述 ∮
''Even if you don't speak.''
∮ 你的眼睛流露了所有 ∮
''Your eyes will reveal everything.''
∮ 我承认你不关心世事 ∮
''I admit that you don't care about the world.''
∮ 但你的父母知道了他们该如何 ∮
''But what will your parents say when they find out.''
∮ 爸爸在等着我和我说好的 ∮
''Daddy is waiting for me to say yes.''
∮ 妈妈也准备好了 ∮
''Even my mother is ready.''
∮ 如果你说愿意  他们会为我们祝福 ∮
''If you say yes then he'll bless us both.''
我能告诉你个秘密吗  爸爸
Shall I tell you a secret, papa?
你不回来  我也不回家
I won't go back home until you don't come back.
多浪漫啊
How romantic.
这就是你所做的
So this is what you do..
任务前后六个月
..six months before and after the jobs.
瑞亚
Rhea.
你误会了
You are mistaken.
你知道我只忠于一个女人
You know I am a one woman man.
那就好
That's fine.
但谁是那个女人呢
But who's that one woman.
我们六个月后才见面
We are meeting after six months.
你就只问我这个?
Have you got only questions for me?
我也给你准备了礼物
I have a gift for you as well.
生日快乐  查理
Happy birthday, Charlie.
不错  - 当然  这是马里卡的画
Nice. - Of course. It's a Malik.
马里卡先生
Malik sir.
那一定很贵
Then it must be expensive.
为什么这么破费
Why spend so much?
我会为你做任何事情  亲爱的
Anything for you, baby.
维克托  你说的太对了
Victor, you were absolutely right.
什么
What?
我见过维克托了
Yes, I met Victor.
他说什么
What did he say?
他没来吗
He didn't come?
我把计划给他了
I've given him the plan.
让我们往好处想吧
Now let's hope for the best.
∮ 主啊  我们是你的信徒 ∮
''Lord, we are your devotees.''
∮ 这是我们义务 ∮
''Such should be our deeds.''
∮ 愿我们追随正义之路 ∮
''May we follow the path of righteousness.''
∮ 避恶行善 ∮
''And shun evil.''
∮ 我们会含笑牺牲 ∮
''So that we can lay down our lives with a smile.''
叫救护车  - 快点
Call the ambulance. - Quick.
救救我  主啊
Save me, Jesus.
医生  求你救救他
Doctor, please save him.
我们还有很多东西要和他学习呢
There's a lot I have to learn from him.
别担心  警官
Don't worry, Commissioner.
救他是我的职责
It's my duty to save him.
布拉干萨先生  你准备好手术了吗
So, Mr. Braganza. Are you ready for the operation?
这非常危险
It's very risky.
不过我已准备面对危险了
But I am prepared to take this risk.
谢谢
Thank you.
但是手术费用很贵  - 我知道
But this operation will be expensive. - I know.
打这个号码
Call on this number.
你会得到全部的手术费
You will get the entire amount for the operation.
人都要死了  他关心的却是费用
A person is dying and he's concerned about the costs.
好吧  警官  我们要开始手术了
Okay, Commissioner, we're going to start the operation..
你们能在外面等着吗  - 祝你手术顺利
..can you please step out.. - Wish you all the best..
别担心
..for the operation. - Don't worry..
手术肯定会成功  - 谢谢
..our operation will surely be successful - Thank you.
我们出去
Let's go.
还有很多东西要和他学习呢
''Still a lot to learn.''
但我们的玩家...
But our players.
你需要的玩家已经准备就绪了
The players that you need are present right here.
爆破专家  比拉尔巴氏
Explosives expert, Bilal Basheer.
从小他只热衷两件事情
Since childhood he has only two passions.
进口汽车和本地炸药
Imported cars and local explosives.
比拉尔  你真牛
Bilal, you are great.
从那以后比拉尔有一只耳朵聋了
And since then Bilal Basheer became Bilal 'Behra' (deaf) with his one ear.
他在每个国家都有情报
Yet, he has contacts in every country.
他会说32种语言
He can speak 32 languages.
擅长爆破和间谍装置
An expert in explosives and spy devices.
你好  - 你好
Hello.  - Hello.
这是桑尼马塔
And he's Sunny Mehra.
易容高手
Master of prosthetics and makeup.
他是想做别的工作的
He actually wanted to be something else.
演员
Actor.
那是沙鲁克汗的风格
'That Shah Rukh Khan style.'
你不撒泼尿照照?
'Have you seen your face?'
滚出去!消失!
'Get out, get lost.'
在约胡海滩画画
'You don't become a hero..
你不会出名的
'..by getting your picture taken at Juhu Beach. - But..'
但从那天起他立志成为
That day he decided he will become an expert..
一名易容高手
..in make up and prosthetics.
但是你得注意提防他
But you will have to stay slightly careful of him.
毕竟他是易容高手
He's a makeup artist after all.
他不会保守秘密
He cannot keep a secret.
你说什么
Did you say anything?
没什么  我说你是真正的艺术家
No, no, I was just saying that you are a fine artist.
你这么说我都有点不好意思了
You are embarrassing me.
你生得就不好意思了
You are born to be embarrassed.
闭嘴  聋子
Shut up, deaf.
什么
What?
没什么  - 不  你说话了
Nothing.  - No, you said something.
是吗
I see.
看起来他们处得不错
Seems like they get along well.  - Yes.
这是罗尼
And he is Ronnie.
印度最伟大的幻象魔术师
India's biggest illusionist.
魔术师
Magician.
因为某些原因罗尼不再表演魔术了
Due to some reasons Ronnie stopped performing magic shows.
感谢上帝  当我问他的时候他同意参加这次手术
But thank God he said yes for this operation when I asked.
谢谢你  罗尼  - 是的  谢谢
Thanks, Ronnie. - Yes, thank you.
你认识的  瑞亚
And you do know Rhea.
兼职汽车专家
Part time automobile expert.
全职艺术家
And full time artist like us.
世界上几乎没有男人
There's hardly a man on earth..
能抗拒她的魅力
..who can resist her charm.
我在报纸上看到那天晚上
And the next day I read in the newspapers..
她不仅伤害了南非排名
..that that night she didn't just break south Africa's..
第七位富豪的心还有他的脸
..seventh richest man's heart but also his safe.
但我们的计划还缺少个人我无法提供
But I couldn't provide you one man according to your plan.
黑客
The hacker.
不是黑客  是世界上最好的黑客
Not the hacker, world's best hacker.
蜘蛛
Spider.
没人知道他是谁  住在哪
No one knows who he is or where he lives.
那有人能替代他吗
So is there an alternative for him?
有人能替代你吗
Is there an alternative for you?
他  他  还是她?
Him, him, or her?
没人能替代最好的
There is no alternative for the best.
你得找到他
You will have to find him.
最后一件事  查理
And one last thing, Charlie.
我违背了诺言
I have broken a big promise.
我要让你偿还
I will make you pay for it.
一克不留
To the last gram.
我听说蜘蛛是最棒的黑客
By the way, I have heard that Spider is the best hacker.
他两次黑进了NASA(美国国家航空航天局)卫星
He has hacked two of NASA's satellites.
他们要去月球
They had to travel to the Moon..
结果却在火星着陆
..but landed on Mars instead.
你们说的是哪个蜘蛛
Which Spider are you talking about?
那只是他的一个朋友
Just one of his friends.
我还以为你们说的是世界上
I thought you are talking about the world's best hacker Spider.
最好的黑客蜘蛛呢
你知道蜘蛛?
You know about Spider.
嗯  一点点
Yes, just briefly.
但一定另有其人
But this must be someone else.
一个会计师要从黑客那里得到什么
What could a chartered accountant want from a hacker?
我感兴趣  南娜
I am interested, Naina.
他从我的账户盗走了数百万美元
He has stolen millions of dollars from my clients.
黑了他们的银行账户
By hacking in their bank accounts.
是吧?  - 是啊  他黑进了我的
Isn't it, guys?  - Yes, he hacked in..
展览室  偷走了所有东西
..and stole my entire showroom.
只剩下了百叶窗
Only left the shutters behind.
你了解蜘蛛多少
How do you know about Spider?
我研究道德黑客攻击
Hello. I have done Masters in Ethical Hacking..
蜘蛛是我的论文课题
..and Spider was my thesis project.
你知道蜘蛛是谁吗  在哪能找到他
Do you know who this Spider is and where we can find him?
有几次我差点找到他
I got this close to finding him couple of times.
我听说他最后一次出现是在香港
Last I heard he was in Hong Kong.
但当我快追踪到他的时候  他跑了
But I lost him before I could track him.
但如果你愿意  我会再试试
But if you want I can try again.
太好了  南娜  再试试
That's great, Naina. Please Try again.
为我们所有人
For all of us.
查理  我困了
Charlie, I am feeling sleepy.
那就睡一会  - 不  我要喝咖啡
Then get some sleep.  - No, I want coffee.
我找到他了  我找到他了
I got him. I got him.
他收到封邮件  他打开了
He got the mail. He fell for it.
我黑进了他的系统
I hacked his system.
蜘蛛是印度人
Spider is an Indian.
你不敢相信  他就在果阿
And you won't believe it, he's in Goa.
什么
What?
有他的地址吗
Can we get his address?
他的邮政地址是
His postal address is.
维埃拉社区304号公寓  安吉拉
Riviera Society.Apartment 304. Anjuna.
我们走
Let's go, guys.
你呆在车上
You stay near the car.
瑞亚   比拉尔
Riya, Bilal.
坐电梯  堵住他的门
Take the lift and cover his door.
罗尼  我们堵住楼梯
Ronny, we will block the stairways.
嘿  送披萨的
Hey, pizza-boy.
披萨还没送出去你怎么就走了
Where are you going without making the delivery?
罗尼  我找到他了
Ronny, I got him.
是送披萨的  他下楼了
It's the pizza-boy and he's coming down.
蜘蛛最后被网捉住了
So finally Spider is caught in the web.
你们没有任何证据证明我就是蜘蛛
You don't have any proof that I am Spider.
你们不能逮捕我
You can't arrest me.
我们不是警察
We are not the police.
那你们干嘛跟着我
Then why are you after me?
我们是来给你建议的
We want to tip you, pizza-boy.
价值一亿元
Worth 100 million.
你需要个团队  查理
You need a team, Charlie.
世界顶尖玩家组成的团队
A team of the world's best players.
什么...
What the..
你能用这些黄金盖一座宫殿了
You can make a palace out of all that gold.
计划是什么
What is the plan?
按条理来说
Putting it in one line..
计划是我们从运输的火车上
..the plan is that we will steal the gold from the train..
把黄金盗走
..in which it is being transported.
你没开玩笑吧
Are you serious?
我们在谈论的是场国际抢劫案
We are talking about an international robbery.
如果是俄罗斯  黑手党也会卷进来的
And if it's Russia's, then the mafia will be involved as well.
你不觉得这是项艰巨的任务吗
Don't you think this is a difficult job?
我还没开始计算难度呢
I haven't even started counting the difficulties.
黄金将由这辆卡车运离沙皇冬宫
The gold will be transported in this truck from the Czar's Winter Palace..
由一个军队护送
..with a military convoy.
黄金将在俄罗斯军事基地被卸载
The gold will be loaded from this Russian Military Station..
装入货箱
..into this cargo container.
货箱有两个锁
There are two locks in the container.
电子的和人工的
Electronic and manual.
电子锁的密码
And the code to this electronic code..
只有一个俄罗斯将军知道
..will be given to one Russian General.
来说说火车
Coming to the train.
装满黄金的货箱
The container filled with gold..
将被装载在这辆火车上
..will be loaded on this train, and..
前后两节车厢
..there will be two coaches ahead and behind it.
运载着俄罗斯突击队员
Filled with Russian Commandoes.
火车的速度会被设定
The train's speed will be set..
卫星追踪火车行程
..and its progress will be tracked by a satellite.
如果方圆一公里内有任何可疑
If anything is detected within a kilometer of its range..
或者火车减速  停靠
..or if the train slows down or stops then..
三分钟之内俄罗斯喷气歼击机将会抵达
..within three minutes Russian Fighter Jets will be scrambled.
俄罗斯政府
And the Russian government..
已经在当地报纸上刊登了这则消息
..has published this information in their local papers.
所以没人想着去碰这批黄金
So no one imagines about touching this gold.
但是  查理  我们怎么做
But, Charlie, how will we do this?
你们的新电话
Your new mobiles.
里面有计划的细节  你们的角色
It contains the plan's details,your individual roles..
还有基本俄语口语教程
..and also a basic Russian speaking course.
如果你想成为大玩家
If you want to be a big player..
你就得冒大风险
..then you have to take a big risk.
恭喜  伙计们
Congratulations, guys.
不久你们就是亿万富翁了
Soon you each be the owners of 100 million.
黄金不是价值十亿元?
Isn't the gold worth 1 billion
我们占了六成
And there are six of us.
你是不是抽扣了?
Are you deducting TDS?
可以这么说
You can say that.
剩下的属于维克托
The remaining share belongs to Victor.
谁是维克托
Who is Victor?
维克托是不登场的团队队长
Consider Victor as the non-playing captain of this team.
这么大的劫案没有他的指导
Committing this big robbery without his guidance..
是不可能成功的
..is impossible.
最重要的事情是
The most important thing.
劫到黄金后我们如何离开
How will we get out after the robbery?
时机成熟你们就会知道撤离计划了
You will know the exit plan when the time's right.
对不起
Sorry, guys. Excuse me.
南娜  - 什么南娜
Yes, Naina. - What Naina?
你答应我如果我找到蜘蛛
You promised me that if I find Spider..
你就会带我出去约会
..then you will take me out on a date.
南娜  真对不起
Naina, I am really sorry.
我也很想见你
Even I wanted to meet you..
但是现在情况紧急
..but something urgent has come up.
我明天早上就得走了
So I am leaving tomorrow.
你得一个人去接维克多了
And you will have to go alone to receive Victor as well.
你要去哪
But where are you going?
去做我一生中最大的买卖
To make my life's biggest deal.
俄罗斯
Russia.
圣彼得堡
喜欢这辆火车吗  - 嗯  不错
Do you like this train?  - Yes, perfect.
他们来了
They are here.
这是我们摄制组
This is our film unit.
女主角
The heroine.
导演
Director.
他是摄影师
He's the cameraman.
助理导演
And he's the assistant director.
化妆兼打杂
Makeup man and spot boy.
在这你至少得把我捧成明星
You could have at least made me a star here.
你们的火车
Your train.
祝你们在俄罗斯拍摄愉快
Enjoy your shoot at Russia.
谢谢
Thank you.
理解一下
Try to understand.
我不能再多说了
I cannot tell you anything more.
我只能说
All I can say is that..
这次之后我不会再让你失望了
..after this I will never disappoint you again.
我能知道你在和谁打电话吗
Can I know who you were talking to?
从俄罗斯的军事基地
There is just one tunnel between..
到罗马尼亚只有一条隧道
..the Russian Military Base and Romania.
火车两分钟就能穿过
And the train will take only two minutes to cross it.
在这两分钟里
And within these two minutes..
丹尼要表演你的魔术
..Ronnie you will have to perform your trick..
蜘蛛要黑进俄罗斯卫星
..and Spider you will have to hack the Russian Satellite.
但我黑进去之后
But after I hack into it..
系统只会关闭十分钟
..the Russian systems will be down only for 10 minutes.
之后系统会重启
After that the systems will restart again.
就是说我们只有十分钟的时间
That means we have just 10 minutes..
实行整个抢劫
..to execute the entire robbery.
你的票
Ticket please.
谢谢
Thank you.
火车怎么走了
How is the train moving?
这个魔术师真是太危险了
This magician really is dangerous.
我已经换了引擎
I have replaced the engine.
现在安装助推器了
And now I am installing this power booster.
如果一切顺利  那辆破旧的柴油火车
If all goes well then this rundown diesel train..
我们想让它跑多快就能跑多快
..will run at the speed that we want.
你好  - 会计师  事情怎么样了
Hello.- Yes, CA, how is everything going?
我们正在进行中  全心投入
We are working on that,completely involved in it.
别太投入了
Don't get too involved that..
而忘了怎么撤离了
..you forget how to get out of there.
明白了吗  - 是的  先生
Understood.- Yes, sir.
蜘蛛
Spider.
维克托发来了撤离计划  打开看看
Victor has sent the exit plan. Check it.
好的
Right.
查理
Charlie.
查理  我黑进了俄罗斯军事网站
Charlie. I have hacked into the Russian Military website.
这有参与运输黄金的
This is the list of officers who will be involved..
军官名单
..in the train that will be carrying the gold.
名字是按照军衔排列的
The names are according to the rank.
就是说最上面的两个将军
That means the two generals on the top..
是安全主管  - 是的
..are security in-charge.- Yes.
米克黑尔莱维斯基将军
Lieutenant General Mikhail Levitski.
蒂莫特锐沃罗宁少将
And Major General Dimitry Yegorov.
比拉尔  我需要这两位将军的所有信息
Bilal, I need all the information about these two generals.
他们吃什么  能喝多少
What they eat? How much they drink?
最重要的是他们住哪
And most important, where they sleep.
比拉尔
Bilal.
嘿   我们需要这两位将军的信息
Hey. We need information about these two generals.
你干嘛大喊大叫
So why are you screaming?
因为...
Because..
算了吧
Forget it.
你的酒  - 过来坐下
Your drink.- Come, sit down.
他就是我们需要的人
So he's our man.
瑞亚
So, Riya.
准备好去见沃罗宁将军了吗
Are you ready to meet general Yegorov?
当然
Of course.
一杯橙汁
One orange juice.
紧张?
Nervous.
不是  就这么干等着
No. But this waiting.. God.
我要喝一杯
I need a drink.
查理  沃罗宁来了
Charlie, Yegorov is here.
∮ 我的身体越来越热 ∮
''It's getting hot.''
∮ 每种酒我都尝试 ∮
''I am drinking every shot in this party.''
∮ 我感觉醉了 ∮
''I am feeling intoxicated.''
∮ 我神志不清  头重脚轻 ∮
''I am so knocked out, my head is getting heavier.''
∮ 不  不  不 ∮
''No, no, no.''
∮ 想知道下一步如何 ∮
''Wonder what will happen next.''
∮　我浑然不觉 ∮
''I am completely numb.''
∮ 酩酊大醉 ∮
''Totally drunk.''
∮ 喝得一干二净 ∮
''I drank it neat.''
∮ 停止你的英国调调 ∮
''Stop this English tune.''
∮ 看我摇摆 ∮
''Watch me sway.''
∮ 跟随心跳 ∮
''To the local beats.''
∮ 天色渐晚 ∮
''As the night grows.''
∮ 我感觉醉了 ∮
''I feel intoxicated.''
∮ 双目迷离 ∮
''I cannot see anything clearly.''
∮ 视线模糊 ∮
''My sight is getting hazier.''
∮ 我要尽情摇摆 ∮
''I will sway to the fullest.''
∮ 每个角落都能摇摆 ∮
''I can swing to every corner.''
∮ 最好有人阻止我 ∮
''Someone better stop me.''
∮ 也许我会亲吻你 ∮
''Or I might kiss you.''
∮ 停止你的英国调调 ∮
''Stop this English tune.''
∮ 看我摇摆 ∮
''Watch me sway.''
∮ 跟随心跳 ∮
''To the local beats.''
∮ 我要把空杯填满吗 ∮
''Should I fill the empty glasses?''
∮ 我想我该如此 ∮
''I think what I should do.''
∮ 我已冒险 ∮
''When I have taken the risk.''
∮ 那么为什么害怕世界 ∮
''So why be afraid of the world.''
∮ 我该何去何从 ∮
''Should I go this way or that?''
∮ 我不知道去路 ∮
''I don't know which way to go.''
∮ 告诉我如何回家 ∮
''You tell me how do I go home in this condition?''
∮ 不  不  不 ∮
''No, no, no.''
∮ 想知道下一步如何 ∮
''Wonder what will happen next.''
∮ 我浑然不觉 ∮
''I am completely numb.''
∮ 酩酊大醉 ∮
''Totally drunk.''
∮ 喝得一干二净 ∮
''I drank it neat.''
∮ 停止你的英国调调 ∮
''Stop this English tune.''
∮ 看我摇摆 ∮
''Watch me sway.''
∮ 跟随心跳 ∮
''To the local beats.''
祝您晚上愉快
Have a nice evening.
你得先唱首歌给我
You have to first sing me a song.
印度人干嘛要把唱歌和性爱搞在一起
Why do Indians always mix singing with sex?
我看过你们的电影
I've seen in your movies.
男主角饥渴  他唱
Hero gets horny, he sings.
女主角饥渴  她唱
Heroine gets horny, she sings.
总是如此
Always.
所以你不喜欢印度人
So you don't like Indians.
我没这么说
I didn't say that.
我们俄罗斯人喜欢拉杰卡普的所有电影
We Russians like all Raj Kapoor movies.
我看过我是一个小丑
I have seen 'Mera Naam Joker'.
流浪者和乡巴佬进城记
'Awaara' and 'Sri 420'.
你骗人  证明给我看  - 好的
You're lying . Prove it.- Okay.
∮ 我的鞋子是日本的 ∮
''My shoes are Japanese.''
∮ 我的裤子是英国的 ∮
''My pants are English.''
还好这首歌里没提到内裤
Thank God there is no mention of underwear in this song.
∮ 我戴的帽子是俄罗斯的 ∮
''The hat I am wearing is Russian.''
∮ 但我有一颗印度心 ∮
''But yet at heart I am an Indian.''
采集到声音样本了
Voice sample recorded.
你看起来很帅
You are looking great.
∮ 我的鞋子是日本的 ∮
''My shoes are Japanese.''
∮ 我的裤子是英国的 ∮
''My pants are English.''
我戴的帽子是俄罗斯的
''The hat I am wearing is Russian.''
但我有一颗印度心
''But yet at heart I am Indian.''
不只你的帽子是俄罗斯的  你的口音也是
Not just your hat but you sound Russian too.
准备时间结束
Planning time is over.
玩家们  我们去拿黄金吧
Players, let's go for the gold.
沃罗宁的司机开着车来了
Yegorov's driver is approaching with the car.
现在
Now.
钉子起作用了
The spikes have done their job.
现在修好你的轮胎
Now you fix your flat tyre.
我们的人去接沃罗宁
And our man will pick up Yegorov.
桑尼  到你出场了  - 好的
Sunny, it's your turn. - Okay.
再见
Goodbye.
安安静静的睡24小时吧
Sleep peacefully for the next 24 hours.
哇哦  真棒
Wow. Great.
可以吗  - 完美
Okay.
- Perfect.
连他老爸都认不出来
Even his father cannot recognize you..
谁让我是桑尼马塔呢
..otherwise my name isn't Sunny Mehra.
祝你好运  查理  - 谢谢
Good luck, Charlie. - Thanks.
把文件拿来给我
Go, get that file.
不是这个  红色的那个
Not this one, the red one.
是的  将军
Yes, sir, General.
照顾好沃罗宁
Look after Yugorov.
别提他了 专心你的工作
Forget him and concentrate on your work.
别开玩笑了
Stop joking.
桑尼  准时就位
Sunny, be in place at the right time.
好吗  - 好的
Okay? - Okay.
马上去检查车厢  - 好的  先生
Go check the carriages, immediately.- Okay, sir.
摄像机安好了
The camera's in place.
太棒了 查理
Great, Charlie.
该放旗子了
Time to put up the flags.
这是俄罗斯和罗马尼亚
This is the symbol of friendship..
友谊的象征
..between Russia and Romania
全体  向后转
Crew, about turn.
015.
920.
61.
03.
58.
好极了  - 耶
Great.- Yeah.
喂  - 罗尼  火车出发了
Hello.- Ronnie, the gold train has departed.
我们准备就绪
Let's get ready.
好了  伙计们
Alright, guys.
我要激活助推器了
I am activating the boosters.
快到隧道了
Guys, Tunnel spotted.
我能看到隧道了
I can see the tunnel.
罗尼  火车要进隧道了
Ronnie, the gold train is about to enter the tunnel.
收到
Okay.
罗尼  现在全靠你的幻象术了
Ronnie, now everything depends on your illusion.
蜘蛛  到你了
Spider, your turn.
各位  不好意思打扰一下
Ladies and Gentlemen, sorry for the interruption.
噢  不
Oh no.
怎么回事  - 我不知道
What's wrong? - I don't know.
快点检查下
Just check, man.
现在启动时间
Your time starts now.
我们只有十分钟
We have 10 minutes.
抓紧  各位  我要增速了
Buckle up, guys. I am increasing the speed.
有结果没
Any result?
先生  系统崩溃了  - 什么
Sir, system has crashed. - What?
快打电话给工程师
Call the engineer, fast!
各位  我能看到火车了
Guys, I can see the train.
幻象术起作用了
The illusion is working.
他们看不到我们的火车
They cannot see our train.
好样的
Good job.
怎么了  - 我们失去联系了
What happened? - We lost connection.
蜘蛛  密码
Spidey, what is the code?
0159.
2061.
20...061
20.- 061.
61... 下面
61.. next.
0358  - 0358
0358.- 0358.
就这个?  - 嗯
That's it - Yeah.
抓住他  - 住手!
Let's get him. - Stop!
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
有什么问题吗
Is anything wrong there?
一切正常
Everything's okay.
四分钟
Four minutes.
罗尼
Ronnie.
怎么了
What happened?
幻象术出问题了  - 什么
There's a problem with the illusion. - What?
我重放了视频
I've rewinded the video.
查理  时间不多了
Charlie, we're losing time.
玩家们  头等大奖
Players, Jackpot.
我们成功了!
Yes, we did it.
爱你  查理
Love you, Charlie.
我们很快就连接到卫星了
Soon we will reconnect with the satellite.
比拉尔  小心
Bilal, watch out.
我们怎么运输剩下的黄金
How will we transfer rest of the gold now?
各位  只剩一分钟了
Guys, we have just one minute.
系统一分钟后重启
And the system will restart in one minute.
要到岔路了  快点  查理
Diversion coming up,hurry up, Charlie.
卫星系统随时可能重启
Their satellite system can restart any minute.
过来  查理  快点
Come on, Charlie, hurry up.
过来
Come on.
过来  查理
Come on, Charlie,
快点  - 别去捡金条了  跳过来
Hurry up.- Forget the gold bar and jump.
过来  查理
Come on, Charlie.
握住我的手
Take my hand.
我们成功了
Yes. We made it.
谢谢  朋友们
Thank you, friend.
回到你们的岗位吧  一切正常
Come on. Get back to your positions.Everything is fine.
先生  我会继续拜访你的
Sir, I will keep visiting you.- Yes, why not? Why not?
好的  干嘛不呢
我很想你  爸爸
I missed you, papa.
我真的很想你
I really missed you.
你会拿你的那份干嘛
What will you do with your share?
我要买这个
I will buy this.
我的梦想大厦在惠灵顿
My dream mansion in Wellington.
下周拍卖
It's being auctioned next week.
底价1000万美元
Starting bid is 10 million dollars.
查理  你不该为一根金条冒这么大的险
Charlie, you shouldn't have taken such a big risk for one gold bar.
罗尼  我答应过维克托
Ronnie, I promised Victor..
我会一克不留的偿还他
..I will pay him to the last gram.
太好了  过去的十年里
How lovely, dear. I missed you and this house so much..
我都在想念你和这栋房子
..in the past 10 years.
所以最好了解这房子的规则
So better understand the rules of this house as well.
你要和谁谈话或见谁  必须通过我
If you want to talk or meet someone, only through me.
好的
Okay.
吃吧  是我做的
Just eat, that's my order.
好
Okay.
喂  - 我们成功了
Hello.- We did it.
我说过什么
What did I say, papa?
本世纪最大的劫案
The largest robbery of the century.
十亿元
1biliion.
现在你的梦想可以实现了
Now your dream will be fulfilled.
我太高兴了
I am so happy.
真希望你能在这
I wish you were here with us.
南娜  我...
Naina, I..- No, papa. No need to say anything.
不  爸爸  别说了
我只问你一件事情
I just asked for one thing.
一个承诺
Just one promise.
你不再做错事
That you won't do anything wrong.
你食言了  只是为了钱
And you broke that. Just for money.
不  南娜  我不是为了钱
No, Naina, I didn't do this for money. - Papa, stop lying.
别编了  爸爸
爸爸  过去的十年里
Papa, for the past 10 years..
我远离你就是不想让你做错事
..I stayed away from you just so that you don't do anything wrong.
但是可能你不爱你的女儿
But maybe you don't love your daughter.
给我次机会  南娜  听我解释
Give me a chance,Naina, let me explain.
敬成功
Alright, to success.
敬世界上最好的团队
To the best team in the world.
敬查理  世界上最棒的玩家
To Charlie. The best player in the world.
比拉尔巴氏
Bilal Basheer.
你可以告诉我们
You have an opportunity to tell us..
你要拿这一亿元做什么吗
..what you will do with this 100 million.
我要花5000万买车
I will buy cars worth 50 million.
最新款的  老式的  所有车型
Latest, vintage. Every model.
剩下的钱呢  - 谁来给这些车的汽油买单?
The rest of the money? - Who will fill petrol in those cars?
你爸爸吗
Your father?
我爸爸没时间理这些无用的东西
My father won't have time for these useless things.
因为他现在开了家工厂
Because he will now open a production house.
推出了桑尼明星
Hazurilal Mehra presents Sunny the Superstar.
魔术师先生  今天你是要和我们分享
Mr. Magician. Will you tell us something today..
还是保持沉默
..or prefer to keep silent.
今天我会告诉你们  - 说吧
No, I can tell you today. - Then tell us.
我会建一幢房子
I will build a house.
里面有世界上所有的奢侈品
A house that has all the luxuries of the world.
只要打一个电话
Where everything's done automatically.
一切都能自动完成
At a single call.
你用你的魔术能做到吧
You could have done that with your magic as well.
魔术什么都做不了
Magic doesn't do anything.
只会摧毁生活
It only ruins lives.
爸爸
'Papa.'
古蒂亚
'Gudiya!'
因为我的魔术  我女儿永久瘫痪了
My daughter was paralyzed forever because of my illusion.
她甚至都不能动
She cannot even move.
但我想把世界上所有的幸福都给她
But I want to give her all the happiness of the world.
她所要求的都能实现
Everything she commands is done.
从不会感觉她无能为力
She never feels that she cannot do anything.
那将是我最伟大的魔术
That will be my biggest magic trick.
罗尼  我希望你用钱能买给她
Ronnie, I hope you can buy every happiness for her..
所有的幸福
..with this money.
我相信会的
I sure will.
如果这些钱不够...
And if this money isn't adequate..
你个混蛋!
You rascal.
他们是谁
Who are they?
他们是谁的人  你应该知道
Whose men are they? You must know.
毕竟  你是世界上最棒的玩家
After all, you're the best player in the world.
噢  别这样  查理
Oh, come on, Charlie.
这些可怜的家伙  我是说
These poor guys, I mean..
不会让世界上最棒的团队伤心
..don't break the hearts of the best team in the world.
告诉他们希拉有一颗慷慨的心
Please tell them their Shaila has a big heart.
她喜欢与人分享
And she shares it with others..
比如她丈夫的秘密
..just like her husband's secrets.
并和你说过
'And I told you that..'
如果我有任何不测  把包裹寄给查理
'..if anything happens to me send that parcel to Charlie.'
纯罗马尼亚黄金  价值...
'Pure Romanian Gold. Which is worth..'
...我们这样的正人君子
'..decent people like us.'
告诉他们你知道
And tell them that you knew..
并不只有你一个人参加了瑞吉的葬礼
..you weren't the only one at Raj's funeral.
我也在那
I was there too.
还有一件事
And one more thing.
一个世界上没人能追踪到的黑客
A hacker whom no one could trace in the world..
轻而易举地就被你找到
..but you just caught him sitting in your dorm.
就像那样
Just like that.
就没人觉得可疑吗
And no one felt anything suspicious.
你都没有发现我  还是我告诉你的
You didn't find me. I told you my whereabouts.
披萨还没送出去你怎么就走了
'Where are you going without making the delivery?'
你以为是我在追你
You thought you are after me.
但是我领先了
But no, I was ahead of you..
一开始就如此
..always a step ahead.
有那么一瞬间我以为
Yes, for a moment I felt that..
你会为自己留张底牌
..you will keep some cards to yourself.
时机成熟你们就会知道撤离计划了
'You will know the exit plan at the right time.'
但之后你又告诉我撤离计划
But then you gave me the exit plan on a platter.
维克托发来了撤离计划  打开看看
'Victor has sent the exit plan,check it. - Right.'
我只是稍稍改变了撤离计划
I just slightly changed that exit plan.
这不是维克托的撤离地点
This place isn't according to Victor's exit plan.
而是我的
It's according to my exit plan.
我的地盘  我的人
My place, my men.
30公里外维克托的人
And some 30 kilometers away from here your Victor's men..
正拿着抢在雪中起舞呢
..would be dancing around in the snow with their guns.
那么  查理  策划大师
So come on, Charlie,the master planner.
告诉我你所知的
Please tell me that you knew this.
没有
No.
但我知道有我的聪明勇敢的队员
But I knew that I can pull off this job.
我能够完成这项任务
With my intelligence,and the courage of my team.
我做到了
And I did it.
你知道你做不到
And you knew that you can't pull off this job.
你只有一条路能获得黄金
You had just one way to get the gold.
欺骗
Deceit.
嘿  蜘蛛
Hey, Spider.
我们随你处置
You can do anything you want with us.
但是记住  维克托不会放过你的
But remember, Victor won't spare you.
我承认我是个坏蛋
I admit that I am the villain of this story.
但兄弟  你得说点我能信的
But my brother, you should give me some credit.
我还能考虑一下
I must have thought something about it.
过去的十年里我远离你
'For the past 10 years I stayed away from you..'
就是不想让你做错事
'..just so that you don't do anything wrong.'
但是可能你不爱你的女儿
'But maybe you don't love your daughter.'
南娜
'Naina.'
亲爱的  呆在里面
'Dear, stay inside.'
呆在里面
'Stay inside.'
爸爸  爸爸
'Papa. Papa.'
真遗憾  查理
I am really sad, Charlie.
一天之内  你失去了你的老师
You lost your Guru, friend and love in a single day.
朋友和爱人
你还想独活吗
Do you still want to live?
罗尼  罗尼
Ronnie, Ronnie.
你去拿黄金  我去救瑞亚
You get the gold, and I will get Riya.
再见
Bye-bye.
南娜  - "对不起"  你不是要说这个吗
Naina, I.. - ''I am sorry'',isn't that what you want to say.
南娜  听我说  - 凭什么
Naina, listen to me.- Why should I?
我还能原谅你什么
And what else should I forgive you for?
原谅你过去的十年里
For the fact that for the past ten years..
假扮我爸爸的会计师?
..you are posing as my father's CA.
原谅你给我爸爸的诱惑
Or for that fact that my father broke his promise..
让他食言了?
..for the greed you gave him.
南娜  我快要找到蜘蛛了
Naina, I am very close to Spider.
你还要和我说多少遍
How many times will you try to explain to me..
是蜘蛛杀了爸爸
..that Spider killed papa?
他杀了他  但你把他推到了枪口下
He shot him but you threw him in front of the barrel.
是你杀了他  查理  - 南娜
You killed him, Charlie. - Naina.
我感到遗憾的是
And what I regret is that..
我爸爸竟然为了钱而答应  - 够了  南娜
..my father agreed just for some money.. - Enough, Naina.
你可以不理解我
I have no regrets that you misunderstood me..
但是不能误解维克托
..but I really regret that you misunderstood Victor.
他不是为了钱而食言
He didn't break your promise for money..
而是为了他的梦想
..but for his dream.
他梦想着建一所印度最大的孤儿院
His dream to build India's biggest orphanage.
这样就不会再有孩子成为维克托或是查理了
So that no child can become Victor or Charlie again.
相信我  南娜
And trust me, Naina.
我会实现他的梦想的
I will fulfill this dream.
对不起  亲爱的  我食言了
'Sorry, dear. I broke my promise to you.'
我想做件事
'I wanted to do something.. '
当你想起我时会感到骄傲
'.. so that you feel proud whenever you think of me.'
感到骄傲  亲爱的
'Feel proud, dear.'
你的梦想一定会实现
Your dream will surely be fulfilled.
你不能一个人完成我爸爸的梦想
You will not fulfill my papa's dream alone.
还有  查理马斯卡伦哈斯
One more thing, Charlie Mascahernas.
我会让你为爸爸的死买单
I will make Charlie pay for the gold and papa's death.
一克不留
Till the last gram.
看哪  维克托回来了
Look.. Victor is back.
这是我们的护照  信用卡还有一些档案
Here are our passports, visas and other documents.
我们要干嘛
Where are we going?
新西兰
New Zealand.
在那发现了蜘蛛的线索
That's where we will find a clue to catch Spider.
记得这个吗
Remember this.
这是我从火车上拿走的最后一根金条
This is the last gold bar that I picked up from the train.
过去一年里  我去过
For the past one year I have been traveling around..
世界上所有的黄金市场
..to all the gold markets in the world..
希望找到能有罗马尼亚
..with a hope to find a dealer who can get me..
金条的交易人
..a similar Romanian gold bar.
我在奥克兰发现一个交易人
I found a dealer in Auckland.
你想要多少
'How many do you want? '
你能有多少
'How many can you find? '
给我一星期时间
'Give me a week.'
到时打电话给我  我老板亲自来交易
'You call when ready, my boss will be here for the deal.'
好吗  - 好的
'Okay?  - Okay.'
两天前那个交易人打电话了
And two days ago that dealer called.
他想要见面
He wants to meet.
奥克兰
你好
Hello.
是的  我们到奥克兰了
Yes, we have reached Auckland.
我们今天见面交易
We should meet today and do the deal.
是的  我老板和我一起
Yes, my boss is also with me.
好的
Okay.
老板是谁
Who is the boss?
过来  我告诉谁是老板
Come, I will show you who the boss is.
你知道谁是老板吗
Do you know who the boss is?
这是我的老板  扎维巴洽先生
This is my boss, Mr. Zhaveri Bazaar.
印度知名的黄金经销商
A well-known gold dealer in India.
你好  巴洽先生
Nice to meet you, Mr. Bazaar.
那么  你想要多少金条
So, Mr. Bazaar, how many gold bars would you like to buy?
一根?
One?
100根?
One hundred?
1000根?
One thousand?
每根四万美元
But my price, $40,000 per bar.
我知道  没关系
I got it. No problem.
每次大买卖前老板都要咨询占星师
Boss wants to speak to the astrologer before the big deal.
我们是印度人
We're Indians, see.
是的  印度人是非常有宗教信仰的
Yes, yes, Indians very religious people.
你好  - 芯片运作了  查理
Hello.- The microchip is working, Charlie.
诸事皆宜
Yes, it's an auspicious phase.
我们走  工作完成了
Let's go, the job's done.
生意谈成了
The deal is.. on.
交易成功后老板喜欢握手
Boss likes to shake hands when the deal's done.
噢  谢谢
Oh yes, thank you.
多有派头啊  先生
What a stalwart, sir.
你没说一句话就和我做成生意了
You made a deal without saying a single word.
多有个性啊
What a personality?
我多想听到这种话啊
My ears were yearning to hear those words.
我奋斗了15年
I struggled for 15 years.
终于找到能理解我真正价值的人了
Finally I found someone who understood my true worth.
其他人像驱赶流浪狗一样对我
Otherwise people would shoo me away like a stray dog.
老板很高兴
Boss very happy deal done.
谢谢
Thank you.
这边
This way.
印度人  非常有信仰  非常疯狂
Indians. Very religious, very crazy.
干得好  扎维巴洽
Good one my Zhaveri Bazaar.
演得不错
You acted well.
现在你知道我是个多了不起的演员了吧
Now you realized what a good actor I am.
但还是得归功于导演
But the credit for this acting goes to the director.
不错
Not bad.
你做这个多长时间了
How long have you been doing this?
七年
Seven years.
七年?
For seven years?
从我七岁起  - 真的?
Since I was seven years old.- Really.
交易人的电话被追踪了
The dealer's call is being traced.
快接啊
Pick it up, please.
怎么样  - 是他
Hello. How are you? - That's him.
蜘蛛  追踪他
That's Spider. Trace it.
很好  先生
I am good, sir.
这次我给你找了桩大买卖
This time I've got a really big order for you.
有多大
How big?
信号来自新加坡
The signal's coming from Singapore.
就是说蜘蛛在新加坡
That means Spider is in Singapore.
1000根
It's a 1000 bars.
1000根?买家是谁
1000 bars? Who is the buyer?
现在在墨西哥
And now it's Mexico.
他的信号在跳跃
He's bouncing his signal.
印度人  先生  - 印度人?
They're Indians, sir. - Indians?
新西兰  蜘蛛现在在新西兰
New Zealand. Spider is right here in New Zealand.
非常有钱的人
Really rich man.
已经谈妥了
It's confirmed order, Sir.
惠灵顿  他在惠灵顿
Wellington. He's in Wellington.
十秒钟  我就能确定他的精确位置了
Ten more seconds and I can confirm his exact location.
已经谈妥了
It's a confirmed order.
你查过他们的底细了吗
You checked their backgrounds.
五秒钟  - 没有  先生
Five seconds. - No, Sir.
什么  你个蠢货
What? You moron.
三秒钟
Three seconds.
但是  先生...
But, sir..
他就不能再多说三秒钟吗
Couldn't he talk for three more seconds?
至少我们知道了蜘蛛在惠灵顿
At least we know that Spider is in Wellington.
这有什么用
What good is that?
惠灵顿这么大  我们上哪找他去
Where will we look for him in this huge Wellington city?
桑尼说得对
Sunny is right.
我们需要线索
We need a clue.
在奥克兰会找到
And we will find that clue here in Auckland.
南娜  你和我去搜查交易人的办公室
Naina, you and I will raid the dealer's warehouse.
我们呢  我们干嘛
And we? What will we do?
做你们一直在做的事情
You two will do what you two always do.
混蛋  我不会饶了你的
Rascal. I won't spare you.
大声点
Say it louder.
混蛋!
Rascal!
住嘴!
Silent.
烧成灰烬  变成骨灰
What burns turns to ember.What die down are ashes.
比拉尔能让这些灰烬复燃
And one who can make those ashes blowup is called Bilal.
克制一下
Control yourself.
如果今天这个锡克教徒发了疯
Because today if this Sikh loses his mind..
他会拆掉很多东西
..he'll take down many with him.
你们是谁
Who are you?
我是印度人  他是巴基斯坦人
I am India. He's Pakistan.
我们在打架  和平常一样
And we are fighting, like always.
但是为什么
But why?
过去的60年我们从不知道
When for the last 60 years we never understood..
为什么要打架  你怎么能知道呢
..why we are fighting then how can you understand.
不是吗  - 对
Isn't it? - Nice.
你要把玩笑当真吗  - 我们走
You're taking this joke seriously. - Let's go.
至少有150条记录
There are at least 150 entries.
查看惠灵顿的交货记录
Check for deliveries in Wellington.
蜘蛛的黄金从那来
Spider's gold comes from there.
快点
Quick.
惠灵顿的有五条
There are five entries for Wellington.
只有这条
And this is the only entry that..
没有供应商的名字和地址
..doesn't have the name and address of the supplier..
但有日期和时间
..but the date and time.
一定是蜘蛛的货  - 对
This must be Spider's delivery. - Yes.
查看这个时候的录像
Check the footage for the date and time on this.
重放
Rewind it.
停下
Stop.
播放
Play.
是某个女孩  查理
That's some girl, Charlie.
上面有人
Someone up there.
放大车牌号
Zoom on the number plate of this car.
记下来
Write it down.
DZG298
DZG298.
我们刚到惠灵顿
We are reaching Wellington.
谢谢你的信息  我们别墅见
Thanks for the information.I will see you at the castle.
好的  谢谢
Alright, thanks.
你是对的  查理
You were right, Charlie.
车牌号是惠灵顿的
The registration number was of Wellington.
明天我们就能查到那辆车的
By tomorrow we will have the name and address..
主人的姓名和地址了
..of that car owner.
地址在这  - 谢谢
Here's the address. - Alright, thanks.
查理  我拿到那女孩的地址了
Charlie, I got the address of that girl.
也许她就是和交易人
Maybe she's the one who came to make the delivery..
见面的那个女孩
..at the gold dealer.
她叫帕米拉
Her name is Pamela.
噢  不  车辆检查
Oh no, check-post.
这车从哪冒出来的
Where did this car come from?
我们通过检查时
By the time we cross this check-post..
也跟丢了她
..we will surely lose her.
对不起  警官  - 什么
Excuse me, officer.
- Yes.
出什么事了吗  我们有点着急
Is there a problem,we're in a bit of a hurry.
博物馆发生了一宗盗窃案
There has been a theft at the museum.
每辆车都要检查
We are checking every car.
查理  她走了
Charlie, she is gone.
把靴子脱了
Open your boot.
南娜
Naina.
什么...她刚还在这
What the.. She was right here.
她去哪了呢
Where did she go?
我们去哪
So, where is it going to be?
你那还是我那
Your place or mine?
右转  - 哦  去你那
Take right.- Oh, your place.
停车
Stop.
这?你要在这做?
Here? We're going to do it here?
在你梦里  亲爱的
In your dreams, baby.
他妈...
What the..
喂  - 南娜  你在哪
Hello.- Naina, where are you?
在蜘蛛的老巢前
Right in front of Spider's web.
那个混蛋买了座这么大的宫殿
The rascal has bought such a huge palace.
他把所有黄金都卖了吗
Did he sell all the gold?
不可能
Impossible.
蜘蛛卖的那部分
Spider is selling only so much..
不至于引起俄罗斯黑手党
..that doesn't attract the Russian mafia..
或俄罗斯政府的注意  - 没错
..or the Russian government.- Correct.
比拉尔  你能设置一套X光线扫描仪吗
Bilal, can you arrange for an x-ray scanner..
可以在别墅里探测黄金在哪
..which can detect the where the gold is in the castle.
没问题
I can make that.
不过谁来运转它
But who will make the software to run it?
我  你当我隐形吗
Am I Mr. India, do I look invisible?
我们怎么忘了
How could we forget?
既然她能找到蜘蛛  她也能找到蜘蛛的黄金
If she can find Spider then she can find Spider's gold as well.
对不对  查理
Isn't it, Charlie?
他今天一定收到生日礼物了
He's surely getting his birthday gift today.
让她喝几杯就可以尽情取乐了
Just get her a few drinks and have the fun of your life.
并不是只有男人才会占便宜
Boys aren't the only one who take advantage..
有时候女人也会
..sometimes girls do too.
你什么意思  - 没什么  只是...
What do you mean? - Nothing, just..
经验之谈
..speaking from personal experience.
哪里来的经验
Who are you talking about?
你生日那晚  我...
On the evening of your birthday, did I..
忘了吧  南娜 别提了
Forget it, Naina, let it be.
告诉我  查理
Tell me, Charlie.
只是...
Just that..
你拉着我的手  让我靠近
..you held my hand and pulled me closer.
然后  我注视着你的眼睛说
After that.. I stared in your eyes and said..
我爱你  瑞亚?  - 什么
..I love you.. Riya.- What?
比拉尔  - 怎么了
Bilal.- What happened?
我刚在超市电视上看到瑞亚了
I just saw Riya on this market's CCTV.
瑞亚?  - 是的  瑞亚
Riya?  - Yes, Riya.
什么  你确定是瑞亚?
What? Are you sure it was Riya?
我确定
I am sure.
瑞亚刚刚就在这个超市
This is the shop where Riya was standing.
瑞亚在那
There's Riya.
你们的车坠落后
After your car crash..
蜘蛛和他的人就走了
..spider and his men left from there.
他们以为我死了  没有管我
And.. they left me there thinking I was dead.
我以为一切都结束了
I thought everything's over.
我也想自我了断
And I wanted to finish myself as well.
但是神有其它安排
But God had other plans.
我的生命只有一个目的
I had just one motive in life.
找蜘蛛报仇
Revenge from Spider.
所以我来惠灵顿找他了
That's why I came to Wellington looking for him.
但是  瑞亚  我们找了他很长时间
But, Riya, it took us so long to find Spider.
你一己之力怎么找到他的
How did you find him all alone?
蜘蛛住的豪宅是我选的
The grand villa Spider lives in was my choice.
我的梦想大厦在惠灵顿
'My dream mansion in Wellington.'
下周拍卖
'It's being auctioned next week.'
底价1000万
'Starting bid is 10 million dollars.
也许有人会和你竞拍
'Maybe someone will bid higher than you.'
我来了之后发现我的猜测是对的
My doubts were confirmed when I came here.
他真的买了那幢房子
He really did buy that mansion.
当时我也在车里
I was in the truck as well.
我怎么就想不到呢
Then why didn't I think of it as well.
没用的  桑尼
It's no use, Sunny.
蜘蛛的住处有高科技防护
Spider lives amongst hi-tech security.
所以直到现在我也无能为力
That's why even I couldn't do anything until now.
现在你可以做你想做的了
You will now do what you couldn't do until now.
因为你不再是一个人了  瑞亚
Because you are no longer alone, Riya.
这个装置能探测里面的黄金  查理
This device can detect gold kept inside, Charlie.
但是我们要拿到黄金
But for that we will have to take it over the gold.
必须进入蜘蛛的别墅
That means we will have to get inside Spider's villa.
但我们怎么进去呢
But how will we do that?
可以的
It's possible.
蜘蛛每晚都从城里的夜总会
Spider calls a new girl every night..
叫一个新的女孩
..from different night clubs in the city.
有时中国人  有时意大利人
Sometimes Chinese, sometime Italian..
有时土耳其人
..or sometimes Turkish.
我有个巴西朋友在那做服务生
I had a Brazilian waiter friend.
蜘蛛叫过她了
Spider had called her as well.
所以我知道
That's how I know.
就是说我们得安排个女孩  - 不行
That means we will have to arrange for a girl. - No.
这是蜘蛛的地盘
This is Spider's city.
我们不能信任任何人
We cannot trust anyone.
我去
I will go.
我是这里
I am the only one in this group..
唯一一个蜘蛛不认识的人
..whom Spider doesn't recognize.
你不了解蜘蛛
And you don't know Spider.
所以你才这么说
That's why you are being nave.
我知道我在说什么
I know what I am saying.
如果你有更好的人选  洗耳恭听
If you have a better alternative then let's hear it..
如果没有  就别插手
..if you don't then just stay out of it.
瑞亚说的对  南娜
Riya is right, Naina.
这不是容易的事情
It is not an easy job.
别把它当成私人问题
Don't take it personally.
这是我个人的
It is personal for me.
我来这就是为了给爸爸报仇
I came here only to avenge my father's death.
今天我有机会了
And today when I have the opportunity..
你却让我原地不动
..you want me to stay put.
不  决不
No. Never.
我要去会会那个混蛋
I am going to face that rascal.
好吧
Fine.
小蜘蛛爬向喷水管
Insy vinsy Spider crawled up the water spout.
掉落的水滴把它淋湿
Down came the rain drop and washed the Spider out.
淋湿
Washed.
不  不
No, no.
给我更衣  宝贝
Dress me up, baby.
打扰一下  女士  这有瓶香槟
Excuse me, ma'am. Here's a bottle of champagne.
还有一张邀请卡给你
With an invitation card for you.
你确定我们能找到需要的车
Are you sure we will get the car we need?
你确定就在这?
Are you sure this is the place?
我的线人告诉我的
This is what my contact told me.
他说这个人是个天才
He said that the guy's a genius.
他能提供给我们各种车辆
He can provide us with every type of car.
有人吗
Anybody there?
马  狗  猴子都在这
The horse, dog and monkey are here.
别担心  我已经给它们粉饰一新了
Don't worry, I will give them a good makeover..
没人能认出它们
..and no one will be able to recognize them.
别害怕  我说的是车
Don't worry, I was talking about the cars.
我在哪见过你吗
I have seen you somewhere.
一定是在阿姆斯特丹见过
You must have seen me in Amsterdam.
但是那不是我
But that wasn't me.
一定是我弟弟  布鲁 乔普拉  B.C
My brother Budh Chopra, B.C.
我是M.C  曼格 乔普拉
I am M.C. Mangal Chopra.
我是星期二夜里11:55出生
I was born on a Tuesday night at 11:55.
他是12点之后出生
And he was born after 12:00.
所以他成了布鲁(星期三)
So he became 'Budh' (Wednesday).
两个身体  一个灵魂
Two bodies and one soul.
我不会放过你的  - 谁  你弟弟?
I won't spare him. - Who? Your brother?
不  是抢劫了我弟弟的珠宝店的那个人
No, the one who robbed my brother's jewelry shop.
把他全毁了
Completely ruined him.
我不会放过他
I won't spare him.
曼格  不是他
Mangal, he isn't the one.
对不起  对不起
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
毕竟我们是双胞胎
We're twins after all.
我们之间有很强烈的感觉
So there's this strong feeling that exists between us.
就像拉姆阿莎  西塔吉塔  卡然阿俊(电影名)
Like, 'Ram Aur Shyam', 'Sita Aur Gita', 'Karan Arjun'.
卡然阿俊不是双胞胎  爸爸
'Karan Arjun' weren't twins, father.
是讲投胎转世的
It was a case of reincarnation.
爸爸说过
Father had said that..
大人说话小孩不应该打断
..we should interrupt when elders are speaking.
他们是你的孩子?
Are they your children?
我说过了
So I was told.
但是他们...  - 有什么疑问吗
But they are..- Do you have a doubt?
没  - 没  你应该
No..- No, you should.
我每天都干这个
I do it everyday.
他们像他们的妈妈
They are like their mother.
他是苏亚卡帕时  他是常德卡帕时
He's Suryaprakash, and he's Chandraprakash.
她是我妻子香缇
She's my wife, Shanti.
阿尼尔卡普的继女  纱卡
Anil Kapoor's step sister. Shakaal.
你好
Hello.
香缇  我们来客人了
Shanti, we have guests.
表现热情点  - 马上
Show some hospitality. - Right away.
喝茶还是洋葱饼?
Tea and onion fritters.
茶里要放姜吗
Brother, you do take ginger in your tea, don't you?
好
Yes.
好的  过来  孩子们  - 妈妈
Okay. Come, sons. - Mother.
我们今天要去神殿
We will visit the temple today.
地道的印度人!
How Indian.
我也改造他们
I modified them as well.
因为车看着像进口的
Because cars look in am imported look.
而外国人比较看中印度货
And foreigners always look good....with Indian values.
先生  果汁  - 谢谢
Sir, juice. - Thank you.
这是我们的拉姆
He is our Ramu.
你好  - 你好
Hello.- Hello.
他一定是第一个有英国佣人的印度人
He must be the first Indian who has enslaved a British.
你说什么  孩子  - 没
Did you say anything, son? - No.
你好  大叔  - 祝福你  孩子
Greetings, uncle. - Bless you, son.
那么什么车...
So, what car..
嘿  大叔走了
Hello. Uncle's gone.
告诉我你想要哪辆车
Tell me which car do you want?
猎豹  沼泽鹿  小狗
Cheetah, Swamp deer, dog.
那辆叫什么  我要它  - 犀牛
What do you call that? I want that.- Rhino.
去吃点东西  我要干活了
Get something to eat, I will ready it.
大叔  叫夫人
Uncle, call aunt.
南娜是聪明的女孩
Naina's a smart girl.
她应付得来的
She will handle it.
我们已经开始接收信号了
We've started receiving signal from the device.
摄像机正常运转
The camera's working as well.
看看他的汽车收藏
Look at his car collection.
比拉尔  你不想买这辆车吗
Bilal, didn't you want to buy this car?
让我看看  宝贝
Show me, baby.
让她进来  宝贝
Let her in, baby.
声音自动化别墅
Voice automated villa.
罗尼的梦想
Ronnie's dream.
这个混蛋不只偷走了我们的黄金
The rascal didn't just steal our gold but also our dreams.
还偷了我们的梦想
下一步
Next.
关闭  宝贝
Cool it, baby.
开门  宝贝
Open the web, baby.
偷了我们的黄金后他活得真是光鲜啊
He's really shining after stealing our gold.
别担心  桑尼
Don't worry, Sunny.
我们会剥去他的光鲜
We'll peel of that shine.
好地方
Nice place.
你是个大款
You are one rich dude.
有些蠢货无法掌管他们的财富
There were some fools who couldn't handle their wealth.
多亏了他们
All thanks to them.
顺便说一下  像你这么漂亮的
By the way, what is a beautiful Indian like you doing here?
印度人在这里做什么
我也想问你同样的问题
I can ask you the same question.
我是来做生意的
Well, I am here on business.
我是来找乐子的
I am here to have some fun.
就是我的菜
I like it.
进来
Come in.
∮ 我们之间为何距离遥远 ∮
''Why is distance between us?''
∮ 让我们靠近些 ∮
''Let's come closer.''
∮ 感觉每次呼吸 ∮
''Feel it in every breath.''
∮ 我醉眼朦胧 ∮
''My intoxication.''
∮ 我魅力无边 ∮
''My charm always works.''
∮ 我美艳诱人 ∮
''My beauty is alluring.''
∮ 我的美貌让你癫狂 ∮
''My Beauty will make you sway.''
∮ 激情在燃烧 ∮
''The passion that's burning in me.''
∮ 你也会如此 ∮
''You will experience it too.''
∮ 不久你就会知 ∮
''You will soon know why lovers..
∮ 恋人为何会为爱而牺牲 ∮
..intentionally lay down their lives for their love.''
∮ 我欲生欲死 ∮
''I am life and death.''
∮ 我是你的初恋和末恋∮
''I am your beginning and end.''
∮ 来我的庇护下起舞 ∮
''Come in my refuge and sway.''
∮ 我孤独  你亦孤独 ∮
''I am lonely and so are you.''
∮ 这是绝好时机 ∮
''It's a beautiful opportunity.''
∮ 让我们彼此相识 ∮
''Let's get to know each other.''
∮ 我不知道如何何时动心于你 ∮
''I don't know how and when I lost my heart to you.''
∮ 我从未察觉 ∮
''I never realized it.''
∮ 我天真的心爱上你 ∮
''My innocent heart fell for you.''
∮ 真正的罪魁祸首宣告无罪 ∮
''The real culprit got acquitted.''
∮ 带走我的心  继续起舞 ∮
''Just take my life and keep on swaying.''
黄金肯定在门后
The gold is surely behind those doors.
先上床  再洗鸳鸯浴
First the bed, baby. Then the Jacuzzi.
关门  宝贝
Close it, baby.
快啊  南娜
Come on, Naina.
找到了
Found it.
地下保险库在这混蛋的浴缸下
The underground vault is below the rascal's Jacuzzi.
发给南娜撤离信号
Send Naina the signal to come out.
你们好
Hello, everybody.
噢  查理
Oh, Charlie.
就像你把瑞亚送到沃罗宁将军那一样
Just like you sent Riya to General Yueberhoff..
你又故技重施
..similarly you sent her to me.
大家出去
Everybody out.
我说出去
I said out.
欢迎来到我的老巢  蜘蛛对苍蝇说
Welcome to my web, says spider to the fly.
当在惠灵顿我发现你们
When I found out that you are alive..
还活着的时候  我真太高兴了
..and here in Wellington,I was really happy.
蜘蛛  今早从家出来时我的车被跟踪了
Spider, my car was followed from home this morning.
不  蠢女人
No you dumb woman.
你从奥克兰就被跟踪了
You're being followed from Auckland.
交易人和你说了我
The dealer who told you about me..
也和我说了你
..also told me about you.
现在你来了
And now that you are here..
我觉得我又要重温旧梦了
..I felt that I will face action once again in life.
但是  查理
But, Charlie.
同样的把戏  同样的思维
The same old tricks,the same thinking.
全都因为你们的愚蠢
And because of your foolishness..
先是那个白痴罗尼  然后是老掉牙的维克托
..first that idiot Ronnie and then that old Victor..
下次提我爸爸名字的时候  请尊重点
Next time you take my papa's name, do it with respect.
你看什么
What are you staring at?
你该庆幸只是我的左手
You should be thankful that it was my left hand.
开门  宝贝
Open the door, baby.
噢  查理拿到枪了
Oh. Charlie has got a gun now.
他要干嘛  朝我开枪?
What will he do? Shoot me. Come on, shoot me.
来啊  开枪啊
你一定会挨枪子的  但没那么容易
You will surely, but not so easily.
首先我要偷走你最珍贵的东西
First, I will steal the thing that's most dear to you.
你的黄金  一克不留
Your gold, to the last gram.
48小时之内
Gone. In the next 48 hours.
公然挑战?
An open challenge?
男人对男人
Man to man.
玩家对玩家
Player to player.
但你不觉得48小时太短了吗
But don't you think 48 hours is too less.
我是说两天内怎么可能...
I mean what can you possibly do in two days..
我两分钟就能冲破你的世界一流的安全防护
When I can bypass your world class security in two minutes..
想想两天我能干什么
..imagine what I can do in two days.
你第一次让我刮目相看  查理  我喜欢
For the first time you impressed me, Charlie, I like it.
48小时
48 hours.
计时开始
And your time starts now.
滴答
Tick-tock.
你密切注视时钟
You keep a watch on the clock.
我密切注视黄金
And I will keep my eye on the gold.
比拉尔  我想我的表快了
Bilal, I think my watch is fast.
还有多久到48小时
How many hours left to 48 hours?
六个小时里你已经问第12遍了
This is the 12th time you are asking in the last 6 hours.
对不起  但我有点紧张
Sorry, but I am slightly tense.
他大拽拽地说48小时
He proudly said 48 hours to him..
但我希望我们别犯二
..but I hope we don't make a fool of ourselves.
如果他能说  他会说72小时
And if he wanted to say, he could have said 72.
会说96小时
He could have said 96.
但是不  他说了48小时
But no, he had to say 48..
我在给他解释...
I was explaining to him..
如果查理说48小时  他一定考虑妥当了
..if Charlie has said 48 then he must have thought of something.
桑尼
Sunny.
我考虑后才说的
I thought about it before speaking.
德波拉斯基从莫斯科来这
It will take Debrovsky that long..
需要这么长时间
..to come here from Moscow.
比拉尔  打电话给德波拉斯基
Bilal, call Debrovsky.
告诉他  他过去一年里
Tell him that the gold he's been looking for..
要找的黄金在惠灵顿
..for the past one year is here in Wellington.
如果他想要
And if he wants it..
48小时内要赶到
..then he should come here in 48 hours.
你说什么  查理
What are you saying, Charlie?
如果俄罗斯黑手党来了
If the Russian Mafia arrive..
他们会把所有黄金都拿走的
..then they will take all the gold.
我们来这的首要目的是复仇
Our first motive to come here was revenge..
不是偷黄金
..and not to steal the gold.
查理说的对
Charlie is right.
和黄金无关
It's not about the gold.
我们打电话给德波拉斯基
We should call Debrovsky.
这次你别插手  南娜
This time you stay out of it, Naina.
是我们从军队抢来了黄金
We stole the gold amidst the military commandoes..
不是你
..and not you.
查理  我们就这么轻易认输?
Charlie, shall we accept defeat so easily.
有些事情比输赢更重要  瑞亚
Some things are bigger than winning and losing, Riya.
打电话给德波拉斯基
Call Debrovsky.
某天你真会杀了我
Someday you will surely kill me.
别担心  亲爱的
Don't worry, baby.
这把枪里装的是假子弹
This gun's still loaded with rubber bullets.
你一定都听到了
You must have heard everything through this microphone.
查理马斯卡伦哈斯
Charlie Mascarenhas.
失败者
What a loser.
他通知了俄罗斯黑手党
He informed the Russian Mafia.
对不起  亲爱的  我没能把他们拖久点
Sorry, baby. I couldn't hold them for long. - It's okay.
没关系
不管是他还是俄罗斯黑手党
Neither him nor the Russian Mafia..
都不能拿到我的黄金
..can reach my gold.
我们的黄金  不是你的
Our gold, not yours.
这正是我喜欢你之所在
Now that's what I like about you.
你的姿态
Your attitude.
那现在呢
But, what now?
我已经有了
I already have.
这正是我喜欢你之所在
Now that's what I like about you.
你快人一步
You're fast.
坏消息  - 怎么
Bad news. - What now?
我从我的线人那收到条消息
I have just received news from my contact that..
蜘蛛从艾克安全机构雇佣了一辆装甲车
..Spider has hired an armor truck from Ace Securities.
就是说48小时前内他要转移黄金
That means he's shifting his gold before 48 hours.
别灰心  桑尼
Don't panic, Sunny.
还有好消息
That's good news.
现在我们从惠灵顿大街抢回黄金
Now we will rob the gold from the streets of Wellington.
就像在印度做的那样
Just like we did in India.
光天化日之下
In broad daylight.
哇哦
Wow.
有什么主意  查理
What an idea, Charlie?
你这么快就想到了
You thought of this so quickly.
这正是我喜欢你之所在
Now that's what I like about you.
你快人一步
You are fast.
你是最快的  亲爱的
You are the fastest, baby.
人间极品
What a bitch.
现在解释下细节
Now explain the plan in detail.
第一步
Plan no.1.
桑尼  找到这座城市的所有地图
Sunny, get all the maps of this city.
街道地图
Maps for the roads.
地下隧道地图
And maps for the tunnels below the roads.
比拉尔
Bilal.
这怎么不通
How could this be closed?
依地图来看这应该有条路
According to the map there should be a road here.
标记
Mark it.
第二步
Plan no.2.
南娜  明天几个小时你得把惠灵顿变成孟买
Naina, tomorrow you will have to turn Wellington to Mumbai for some hours.
惠灵顿最大的交通堵塞
Wellington's biggest traffic jam.
没问题  查理
It will be done, Charlie.
我们印度人喜欢引起交通堵塞
And anyway, we Indians love causing a traffic jam.
第三步
Plan no.3.
瑞亚  你负责我们的撤离计划
Riya, you begin our exit plan.
比拉尔帮你找艘船
You will find a ship with the help of Bilal..
我们用它把黄金从新西兰运走
..which we will use to transport gold out of New Zealand.
你的钱  - 好的
Here's your money.  - Okay.
谢谢  - 谢谢
Thanks.  - Thanks.
那是你的船
That's your ship.
最重要的
And the most important.
我们要有车
We will have to arrange for cars..
小巧而又速度最快
..that look small but are the fastest on road.
太棒了
Amazing.
时间刚刚好  查理
Perfect timing, Charlie.
即使千金压顶
Even with all the weight..
车丝毫都不会减速
..the cars didn't slowdown at all.
看到没
Did you see?
我的老鼠车的神奇
The marvel of my mice.
他们能够随意进出
They can get in anything,get out of anything..
装载任何重量的东西
..and carry any number of weight.
如果你用它们参加比赛
If you use them in a race..
肯定能赢得黄金
..they will surely win the gold.
这正是我们想要的
That is exactly what we want to do.
我是说别的事情
There was another thing.
和我说说
Tell me.
太好了
Great.
你升级了
You've been promoted.
我会把所有黄金都装在这
I will get all the gold in this.
你的腿能够着那吗  - 当然
Do your legs reach down there?  - Yes.
当然能
Of course they do.
我能知道你在和谁打电话吗
'Can I know who you are talking to? '
她可能回家了
'She might have gone home.'
我女儿不能接电话
'My daughter cannot pick up the phone.'
是照看她的护士
'There's a nurse that stays with her.. '
给我打电话  让她和我说话
'.. who calls me up and lets her talk to me.'
如果这违反了你的规则
'But if this is against your rules.. '
我就叫她不要打过来
'.. then I will tell her not to call me.'
毕竟我是为她才这么做的
'After all, I am doing this for her.'
没有规则
'There is no such rule.. '
可以阻止一位父亲和女儿通话
'.. that can stop a father from talking to her daughter.'
嘿  小超女
Hey, Supergirl.
我不想和你说话
I don't want to talk to you.
看来古蒂亚和我生气了
Seems like Gudiya is angry with me.
当然
Of course.
上周你骗了我
You have been fooling me for the past one week.
"我很快就来了"  "我很快就来了"
''I will come soon, I will come soon.''
你什么时候来见我
When will you come back to me?
马上
Soon.
你会带来惊喜吗
And the surprise that you were supposed to bring along?
我没有见你就是为了准备惊喜
I stayed away from you because of that surprise.
一个大大的惊喜
It's a big surprise.
所以花费了很长时间
That's why it took really long to get it.
这次你来会教我魔术  是吗
And you will teach me magic when you come this time, won't you?
我告诉了我所有的朋友
I have told all my friends..
长大后我会成为一名魔术师
..that I will become a magician when I grow up.
就像我爸爸一样
Just like my papa.
再没人能像我爸爸一样
There is no one else like my papa.
对不对  - 对  宝贝
Yes or no? - Yes, dear.
没人和你爸爸一样
There is no one like your papa.
拜  古蒂亚  - 拜
Bye, dear.- Bye.
敬罗尼和维克托
This one's for Ronnie and Victor.
干杯
Cheers.
祝愿最好的玩家获胜
May the best player win.
快点  小伙子们
Hurry up, boys.
桑尼  进来
Sunny, come in.
桑尼在  说吧
Sunny, here. Go ahead.
你就位没  - 嗯  当然
Are you in position? - Yes, of course.
我在等黄金
I am waiting for the gold.
查理  你是对的
Charlie, you were right.
各位  游戏开始
Game on, guys.
南娜  跟着那辆卡车
Naina, follow the truck.
好的
Okay.
欢迎来到孟买
Welcome to Mumbai.
噢  该死
Oh no.
到底什么情况
What the hell is going on?
检查系统
Check the system.
快点
Check quickly.
该死的  你们...
God damn it, you..
想要右转  对吗
You wanted to right, didn't you?
现在你要左转了
Now you will go left.
桑尼  我的任务完成  到你了
Sunny, my job's done and yours begins.
好的
Okay.
来吧  我的小宝贝
Come to me, my darling.
来把黄金给我
Come and give me the gold.
让开  让开
Move it, move it.
准备比赛  各位
Ready for the race, guys.
三个数  快速左转
At the count of three, sharp left.
三
Three.
二
Two.
一  转!
One, go.
噢  又来了 该死的
Oh no. Not again. God dam it.
你干嘛生气啊
Why are you getting angry?
才一点点嘛
Just a little bit more.
比拉尔  - 准备好了
Bilal.- I am ready.
桑尼  把卡车带到标记处  - 好的
Sunny, bring the truck on the mark.- Okay.
查理  他已经到隧道了
Charlie, he's ready to plunge in the tunnel.
好  再见
Okay, bye.
一会见
See you later.
计划真绝  查理
What a plan, Charlie.
我从未想过你偷了我的黄金
I never realized when you stole my gold.
礼物...  在这...
Gift. Gift. Gift. Its here,its here, its here.
你在那干嘛
What are you doing here?
按我们说的做
Just do as we told you..
去你该去的地方
..and get to the place where you were supposed to be.
就让我看一眼黄金吧
Just let me see the gold once.
看了我就走
And then I will leave.
桑尼  黄金不在卡车里
Sunny, the gold isn't in the truck.
卡车是空的
The truck is empty.
空的?
Empty?
卡车进出别墅的时候
I checked the tire pressure of the truck..
我检查了轮胎的压力
..while entering and exiting the villa.
都是一样的
They were both the same.
那你们还劫这辆车?
They why did you heist this truck?
这样盘旋在你上方的那只鸟
So that the bird hovering above you..
才会觉得我们中计了
..thinks that we have fallen for his trap.
现在他可以毫无警戒地运送黄金了
And now he can easily get the gold out.
就是说他从别的地方运送黄金?
That means he's shifting the gold from somewhere else?
我们走
Let's go.
帕米拉  装载黄金
Pamela, get the gold.
直接来我的机场  - 收到  老板
And come straight to my airstrip.- Sure, boss.
帕米拉
Yes, Pamela.
我们要出来了
We're coming out.
我们已经在出口了
Yes, we're ready at the exit point.
走
Move.
卡车来了
The truck's coming.
准备好
Get ready.
三  二  一
Three, two, one.
去死吧
Get ready to die.
那是我的右手
That was my right.
喂
Hello.
说话  贱人
Speak up you bitch.
你的贱人已经挂了
Your bitch is gone.
你是下一个
You're next.
你是谁  - 你老爸
Who? - Your father.
我拿走了你的黄金
I am taking your gold.
爱咋咋地
Do whatever you like.
查理
Charlie.
是的  老板
Yes, boss.
山姆  你个白痴  黄金被偷走了
Sam you fool, the gold has been stolen.
进去杀了他们  - 好的  老板
Go inside and kill them.- Okay, boss.
出发
Come on, guys.
快点  快点  一切顺利
Come on, come on, all the best.
快点扔
Come on, throw it, throw it.
太好了  他们摔倒了
Great, they fell down.
喂  - 查理  你在哪
Hello.- Charlie, where are you?
我们要去码头湾
We are reaching Marina Bay.
都准备好了吗  - 当然
Is everything ready? - Absolutely.
我等你们
I am waiting for you.
码头湾
Marina Bay.
小心点  伙计们  别伤着他们
Careful, guys, don't hurt them.
惊喜  惊喜
Surprise. Surprise.
在这故事里扭转局面已经成为我的习惯
It's become a habit for me to bring twist in the story.
就像算计也成为了你的习惯一样  查理
Just like it's become your habit to become predictable, Charlie.
还有个惊喜给你
There's another surprise for you.
你的老朋友
Your old friend.
你觉得你在超市偶遇她
You thought you met her again in the Mini Market.
但原谅我  朋友们
But forgive me, friends.
实际上她一直在监视你们
She was actually keeping a watch on all of you.
你为什么要这么做
Why did you do this?
我别无选择  查理
I didn't have a choice, Charlie.
我能怎么办呢
What could I do?
一个无助的女孩不得不独自面对这个世界
A helpless girl who had to face the world alone..
她必须实现自己和年迈的父母的梦想
..she had to fulfill her dreams and of her old parents.
你不想听这样的故事吗?
Isn't that the kind of story you want to hear?
扯蛋  事实是我总想与胜者同行
Crap. The truth is I always wanted to be with the winner.
在莫斯科俱乐部的那晚  我找到了胜者
And that night in Moscow's club I found my winner.
紧张?
'Nervous.'
不是
'No.'
就这么干等着
'But this waiting is.'
我要喝一杯
'I need a drink.'
对不起  - 没关系
'Sorry. - It's okay. '
一杯苹果马丁尼
'One apple martini please. .'
蜘蛛  给我支烟
'Spider, give me a cigarette.'
我不抽烟
'I don't smoke.'
那这包烟是谁的
'Then whose packet is this? '
这又是什么
'And what is this? '
我们抢劫后的撤离计划
'Our exit plan after the robbery.'
聪明  蜘蛛
'Smart, Spider.'
如果我不告诉他们呢
'What if I don't tell this to anyone? '
实际上我有得选择
Actually speaking I did have a choice..
我可以告诉你们蜘蛛的计划
..and I could have told you about Spider's plan.
但是没有蜘蛛任务完成不了
But the mission was impossible without Spider.
我的回报是什么
And what would I get in return?
Z E R O  一分没有
Z E R O.
这么说为了钱你就...
That means just for the money you..
闭嘴  别动
Shut up. Stop this charade.
告诉我黄金在哪
Tell me where is it?
这地方这么大  在哪都行啊
It's a big place, it can be anywhere.
我的黄金在哪
Where is my gold?
黄金在哪
Where is the gold?
什么...  黄金在哪
What the.. Where is the gold?
惊喜  惊喜
Surprise. Surprise.
如果黄金不在车里  会在哪呢
If the gold isn't in the car then where is it, Spider?
对不起  瑞亚
Sorry, Riya.
我也没得选择
I didn't have a choice either.
你坐拥五亿元
You were sitting on 500 million.
为什么还要从惠灵顿博物馆偷油画呢
So why did you have to steal the painting from the Wellington Museum?
她走了
'She is leaving.'
你该退休了
You could've retired.
但是只有警察会退休  贼不会
But then, only policemen retire, not thieves.
他知道了  他知道你所有的事情
He knew. He knew everything about you, you dumb woman.
你个蠢女人
你干嘛责骂这个蠢女人  蜘蛛
Why are you scolding this dumb woman, Spider?
在她习惯面前她那么无助
She was helpless before her habit.
你才是真正的蠢货
You are the real fool.
谁让你在你的别墅
Who asked you to put up that same stolen painting..
挂着那副失窃的油画
..in your villa?
开门  宝贝
Open the door, baby.
五亿元  他会在别墅里挂什么
500 million, and what does he put up in his villa?
一幅失窃的油画?
A stolen painting?
犯贱要有度
There's a limit to being cheap.
听到这些无话可说了吧
Speechless after hearing all this.
我希望你的表还没坏
But I hope your watch is working.
滴答
Tick-tock.
还有一个小时到48小时
There's still one hour left to 48 hours.
你知道你最大的问题是什么吗  蜘蛛
Do you know what your biggest problem is, Spider?
你一直领先
You're always ahead.
走在前面的人
And the one who walks ahead..
不会意识到身后整个游戏的变化
..never realize when the entire game has changed behind them.
故事的转折在于
And as far as the twist in the story is concerned..
你怎么能忘了事情最后总是会倒向好人的
..how can you forget that the last twist belongs to the hero..
而不是坏人
..and not the villain.
现在像你这种傻瓜都能明白这种转折
Now even a fool like you can understand this twist.
我给你的都是你想听到的信息
I gave you the information that you wanted to hear.
德波拉斯基
'Call Debrovsky.'
我知道听到俄罗斯黑手党
I knew that Spider would come out of his web..
蜘蛛会亲自出马
..after hearing about the Russian mafia.
确实如此
And you did.
了如指掌
How predictable.
不  查理
No, Charlie.
我来告诉你谁神机妙算
I will tell you who is predictable.
我可以用枪指着这里的任何一个人
I can point a gun at anyone here I want.
但我会指着这个背叛你的贱人
But I will point this gun at..the bitch who betrayed you.
你在干什么  蜘蛛
What are you doing, Spider?
安静
Quiet.
你已经没用了
Your expiry date is gone.
虽然过去的六个月
And anyway, you have already given me..
你也给了我全部的信息
..all the information you had to in the last six months.
但就忠诚而言...
And as far as loyalty is concerned..
你能背叛像查理这样的好人
..so when you can betray a nice guy like Charlie..
你怎么能对我忠心呢
..then how can you be loyal to me?
冷血贱人  这次枪里是真正的子弹
Chill bitch, this time there are real bullets in the gun.
我让你伤心了吗
Did I break your heart?
查理  你知道吗
Charlie, do you know..
为什么她让我用假子弹射杀她
..why she asked me to put up that charade of fake bullets?
因为她不想让你伤心  查理
Because she didn't want to break your heart, Charlie.
不想在你死前
She didn't want you to know that she betrayed you..
让你知道她背叛了你
..before you died.
你可以杀了他  但不能让他伤心
You can kill someone but not break his heart.
女人  我告诉你
Women, I tell you.
我在试探那个好人
So my predictable good man.
告诉我黄金在哪
Tell me where my gold is.
这就是你选的胜者?
So he's the winner you chose?
快点  查理  说啊
Come on, Charlie. Tell me.
告诉我  查理
Tell me, Charlie.
我时间可不多了
I don't have all the time.
告诉我  查理  否则我杀了她
Tell me, Charlie, or else I will shoot her.
你在浪费我的时间  查理  我要杀了她
You are wasting my time now, Charlie, I will shoot her.
等等
Wait.
我告诉你
I will tell you.
瑞亚
Riya.
对不起  查理
Sorry, Charlie.
当时我别无选择
I didn't have a choice then.
但现在可以了
But I do now.
瑞亚
Riya.
比拉尔
Bilal.
打他
Hit him.
我们还是不知道黄金在哪
We still don't know where the gold is.
我会后悔的就是我没有杀了你
All my life I will regret that I couldn't kill you.
小蜘蛛爬向喷水管  掉落的水滴把它淋湿
Down came the rain drop and washed the Spider out.
老大  找你的
Chief, there's a call for you.
好
Okay.
你好
Hello.
罗马尼亚黄金?
Romanian gold?
在惠灵顿哪里
Where in Wellington?
哪里  哪里
Where? Where?
我们走
Let's go.
还有三辆车?
Which are these three cars?
等等  等等
Just a minute. Just a minute.
我来告诉你怎么回事
I will tell you the test of these three cars.
现在我明白了
So now I understand.
你把装黄金的车留在这了
You left the gold filled cars here.
开走的是空车
And took these empty cars.
太有才了  查理
Great, Charlie.
这全得感谢M.C他们一家人
All thanks to M. C and his family.
你们是印度人
You are Indians.
我甚至会为印度人牺牲自己
And I can even lay down my life for Indians.
走
Go on, go on.
如果他们再在久一点
If they had waited a little while longer..
他们就能吃到洋葱饼了
..they could've taken the veneration offerings.
亲爱的  他们已经有所回报了
My darling, they have got their reward.
现在我要看看洋葱饼  然后给你回报
Now I will conduct the veneration and give you your reward.
走吧  - 不  不
Come on. - No, no.
走  别拒绝
Come on. Saying no to offerings.
各位  俄罗斯黑手党
Guys, Russian Mafia.
大家冷静
Everyone be cool.
别和他们发生冲突
No one will argue with them.
检查他们的车
Check their cars.
但是先生...  - 闭嘴
But, sir, please.. - Shut up.
明白吗
Understand.
空的
Empty.
没有黄金
No gold.
没有黄金?
还没在车里
It's not in this car either.
那黄金在哪
Then where is the gold?
闭嘴
Be quiet.
你看起来生气了
You look angry.
今天别和我顶嘴
Look, don't lock horns with me today.
我损失了一亿元
I have suffered a loss of 100 million.
我冒着生命危险去抢劫黄金  我得到什么了
I put my life at stake to get the gold and what did I get?
屁也没有
Zilch.
我回家怎么和我老爸交代?
What will I tell my father when I return home?
你可以把车给你爸爸
You have the cars for your father.
什么车
What car?
忘了吧
Forget this.
把香槟给他  - 嗯  给我点毒药
Give him champagne. - Yes, give me some poison.
喝香槟而不是毒药
Drink champagne and not poison.
至少还有这辆车
At least spare this car.
这是唯一的纪念品
That's the only memorabilia.
噢  这是黄金做的
Oh my, it's made of gold.
其它的也是吗
And the rest of the cars?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
你用钢和铁制造汽车吗  - 黄铜  铜...
Do you make cars only of steel or iron.. - Brass, copper..
纤维  热熔胶  任何你想要的
..fiber, thermocol, anything you want.
黄金  - 我...
Gold.  - I..
黄金?  - 黄金
Gold?  - Gold.
你是说黄金不在车里
You mean the gold wasn't in the car..
车就是黄金做的?
..the car was made of gold itself.
叔叔  请和我合张影吧
Uncle, autograph please.
当人们见到我的金轮胎时
People will be stunned..
一定大吃一惊
..when they see the gold tires of my car.
哇哦  - 说话  孩子
Wow. - Say it.
开门  爸爸
Open the gate, papa.
∮ 我们之间为何距离遥远 ∮
''Why is distance between us?''
∮ 让我们靠近 ∮
''Let's come closer.''
∮ 感觉每次呼吸 ∮
''Feel it in every breath.''
∮ 你醉眼朦胧 ∮
''My intoxication.''
∮ 你魅力无边 ∮
''Your charm always works.''
∮ 你美艳诱人 ∮
''Your beauty is alluring.''
∮ 你的美貌让我癫狂 ∮
''Your Beauty makes me sway.''
∮ 我被你迷住 ∮
''I am enchanted by you.''
∮ 你的毒魔就像梦儿 ∮
''Your intoxication is like a dream.''
∮ 你的美貌让我癫狂 ∮
''Your Beauty makes me sway.''
∮ 你在我心中  我的问题和答案 ∮
''You dwell in my thoughts, my questions and my answers.''
∮ 你是我的欲望 ∮
''You are my desire.''
∮ 你是我的激情 ∮
''You are my passion.''
∮ 我因你而活 ∮
''My life depends on you.''
∮ 永远和我在一起 ∮
''Always stay with me.''
∮ 现在你已成为我的瘾 ∮
''You have now become my habit.''
∮ 不只是我的瘾  我需要你 ∮
''Not just my habit, but I need you.''
∮ 让我拥你入怀  尽情舞动 ∮
''I take you in my and sway.''